sbtech.com 2019-12-09

# Privacy Policy - SBTech

### **PRIVACY POLICY**

###### 1\. Our Commitment to You

> SBTECH and its affiliated companies (together:  **“SBTech”** ) are dedicated to providing its contacts and clients with the highest levels of transparency and control over the use of their data. In order for us to provide you with our services, we collect and process certain personal information about you and your activity.
> 
> When you entrust us with your information, you can rest assured of our commitment to keep such information private. We have taken measurable steps to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of this data and encourage you to review the following information carefully.

###### 2\. Grounds for data collection

> Processing of your  **“Personal Data”**  (meaning any information which may potentially allow you to be identified by reasonable means) is necessary for the performance of our contractual obligations towards you, for providing you with our services and for the operation of our website ( **“Services”** ), to protect our legitimate interests, and for compliance with legal and regulatory obligations to which we are subject.
> 
> When you use our Services, you consent to the collection, storage, use, disclosure and other uses of your Personal Data as described in this Privacy Policy.

###### 3\. How do we receive data about you?

> We receive your Personal Data from various sources:
> 
>   * _3.1._     Registration information – when you voluntarily provide us with your personal details in order to contact us or register for our Services (for example, your name and email address);
>   * _3.2._     When you communicate with us – for example, when you send us an email, we collect the Personal Data you provide us with.
>   * _3.3._     Technical information – when operating our Services, weuse various technological tracking tools to collect informationregarding your use of the website. Along with our partners, we may use tracking technologies such as cookies, JavaScript,beacons and Local Storage such as HTML5, which are used to store your content information and preferences. You can learn more about the tracking tools we use by reviewing our Cookie Policy.
>   * _3.4.  _   Third party information – we may receive your data from third party providers which help us with the provision and maintenance of our Services, such as analytics vendors,professional or social networks, and others.
> 

###### 4\. What type of data do we collect?

> **Personal Data**
> 
> When you use our Services, we may ask you to provide us with certain Personal Data to provide and improve the Service, to contact or identify you, to enable you to access certain parts of our website, and for purposes otherwise indicated in this Policy. We collect the following Personal Data about you:
> 
>   * _4.1.  _    **Registration information**  – your name, your mailing address, your email address, your telephone number, information about your company and your position, and similar contact details.
>   * _4.2._      **When using our website**  – our web server will collect your IP address, and information about your general location (such as city and country).
>   * _4.3.  _   **Information from third parties**  – this category includes information we receive from our business partners. This may include Personal Data such as your contact details (name, phone, email) as well as details pertaining to your company, your job description, etc.
> 

> 
> **Non-Personal Data**
> 
> We also collect data about the use of our Service and the characteristics and activities of users, in order to operate and improve it. We may collect the following non-Personal Data:
> 
>   * _4.4 **.**_ **     Technical information** – this category includes data such as website visits, the browser you are using and its display settings, your operating system, device type, session start/stop time, referral URL, time zone, network connection type (e.g., Wi-Fi, cellular), and cookie information.
> 

> 
> If we combine Personal Data with non-Personal Data, the combined data will be treated as Personal Data. Further Personal Data will only be stored and processed if you voluntarily provide it to us, e.g. through a contact form.

###### 5\. Tracking Technologies

> When you visit or access our Services we use (and authorize 3rd parties to use) pixels, cookies, events and other technologies. These allow us to automatically collect information about you, your device and your online behavior in order to enhance your navigation of our Services, improve our Services’ performance, perform analytics and customize your experience. In addition, we may merge data we hold with data collected through these tracking technologies as well as data we may obtain from other sources and, as a result, such data may become Personal Data.
> 
> To learn more about our Tracking Technologies please visit our [Cookie Policy](https://www.sbtech.com/cookie-policy/) page.

###### 6\. How do we use the data we collect?

  * _6.1._      **Provision of service**  – your Personal Data is used for the provision and improvement of our Services, including for support and to respond to your queries.
  * _6.2.  _    **Service announcements**  – we will use your Personal Data to communicate with you, to keep you informed of the latest updates to our Services and to provide with you service offers.
  * _6.3.   _   **Marketing purposes**  – we may also use your Personal Data(such as your email address or phone number) to promote our services or those of our partners. For example, by subscribing to our newsletter you will receive tips and announcements straight to your email account. We may also send you promotional material which we believe may interest you, including, but not limited to, by building an automated profile based on your Personal Data. You may choose not to receive our promotional or marketing emails(all or any part thereof) by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link in the emails that you receive from us. Please note that even if you unsubscribe from our newsletter, we may continue to send you service-related updates and notifications or reply to your queries and feedback you provide.
  * _6.3.1._   **Opt-out of receiving marketing materials**  – if you do not want us to use or share your Personal Data for marketing purposes, you may opt out, in accordance with this “Opt-out” section. Please note that even if you opt out,we may still use and share your Personal Data with third parties for non-marketing purposes (for example to fulfill your requests, communicate with you and respond to your inquiries). In such cases, the companies with whom we share your Personal Data are authorized to use your Personal Data only as is necessary to provide these non-marketing services.
  * _6.4._      **Analytics, surveys and research**  – from time to time, we may conduct surveys or test features, and analyze the data we hold to develop, evaluate and improve these features, to improve our Services and create new features for our users.
  * _6.5.  _    **Protecting our interests**  – we may use your Personal Data,when we believe it is necessary, to take precautions against liabilities, investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, investigate and protect ourselves from fraud, protect the security or integrity of our Services and to protect the rights and property of SBTech, its users and partners.
  * _6.6._      **Enforcing of policies**  – we may use your Personal Data to enforce our policies, including, but not limited to, our client agreement.
  * _6.7._      **Compliance with legal and regulatory requirements**  – we may use your Personal Data to investigate violations, and as required by law, to comply with regulatory or other government alauthorities, or to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process.

###### 7\. With whom do we share your Personal Data?

  * _7.1._     **  Internal concerned parties** – we share your information with companies in our group, as well as our employees, to provide you with our services.
  * _7.2._      **Business partners**  – we share your information with business partners, such as storage and analytics providers, which help us provide you with our Services. These third parties may have access to your Personal Data in order to perform these tasks on our behalf, but they are obligated to comply with this Privacy Policy and may not use your Personal Data for any other purposes. More information on our data-sharing with 3rd partie scan be found in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.sbtech.com/cookie-policy/).
  * _7.3.  _    **Compliance with laws and law enforcement entities**  – we cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any data about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, at our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process(including, but not limited to, subpoenas), to protect our or a thirdparty’s property and rights, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical, inappropriate or legally actionable. We may also be required to disclose an individual’s Personal Data in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including meeting national security or law enforcement requirements.
  * _7.4.  _    **Mergers and acquisitions**  – we may share your data if we enter into a business transaction such as a merger, acquisition,reorganization, bankruptcy, or sale of some or all of our assets.Any party that acquires our assets as part of such a transaction may continue to use your data in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

###### 8\. Transfer of data outside the EEA (for EU data subjects)

> Some data recipients may be located outside the EEA. In such cases, to the extent applicable to your Personal Information as an EU data subject, we will transfer your data only to countries approved by the European Commission as providing adequate levels of data protection, or enter into legal agreements ensuring an adequate level of data protection.

###### 9\. How we protect your information

> We have implemented various administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to help prevent unauthorized access, use, or disclosure of your Personal Data. Your data is stored on secure servers and is not publicly available. We limit access to your information to employees or partners and only on a “need to know” basis, in order to enable the carrying out of the agreement between us.
> 
> While we seek to protect the confidentiality of your information, we cannot absolutely guarantee its security. You need to help us prevent unauthorized access to your account by protecting your password appropriately and by limiting access to your account. You will be solely responsible for keeping your password confidential and for all use of your password and your account, including any unauthorized use. You should also be aware that there is always some risk involved in transmitting information over the internet. While we strive to protect your Personal Data, we cannot ensure or warrant the security and privacy of your Personal Data or other content you transmit using our Services, and you do so at your own risk.

###### 10\. Retention

> We will retain your Personal Data for as long as is necessary to provide our Services, and as required to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies. Retention periods will be determined taking into account the type of information that is collected and the purposes for which it is collected, bearing in mind the requirements applicable to the situation and the need to destroy outdated or unused information at the earliest reasonable time. Under applicable regulations, we will keep records containing clients’ personal data, trading information, account registration documents, communications and any other information, as required by applicable laws and regulations.

###### 11\. User Rights

> You may request to:
> 
>   * _11.1.  _Receive confirmation as to whether Personal Data concerning you is being processed, and access your stored Personal Data, together with supplementary information.
>   * _11.2.  _Receive a copy of the Personal Data you directly volunteer to us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format.
>   * _11.3.  _Request rectification of your Personal Data that is under our control.
>   * _11.4.  _Request erasure of your Personal Data.
>   * _11.5.  _Object to the processing of Personal Data by us.
>   * _11.6.  _Request to restrict processing of your Personal Data by us.
>   * _11.7.  _Lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority.
> 

> 
> However, please note that these rights are not absolute, and may be subject to our own legitimate interests and regulatory requirements.

###### 12\. How to contact us

> If you wish to exercise any of the aforementioned rights, or receive more information, please contact: [Privacy@SBTech.com](mailto:privacy@SBTech.com).

###### 13\. Our Policy toward Children

> We understand the importance of protecting children’s privacy, especially in an online environment. Our Site and Services are not designed for / or directed at children under the age of 16 years ( **“Minors”** ). We do not knowingly collect Personal Data from Minors. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Data, he or she should contact us using the details provided above.

###### 14\. Updates to this Policy

> This Privacy Policy is subject to change from time to time, at our sole discretion. The most recent version will always be posted on our website (as reflected in the “Last Updated” heading). You are advised to check for updates regularly. We will notify you in the event of any material changes. By continuing to access or use our Services after any revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the updated Privacy Policy.
